<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="rss.css" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>gabubu news</title>
  <link>https://gabubuavailable.github.io/news/</link>
  <description>News about Wii and tech related</description>
  <item>
    <title>Good news and Bad news</title>
    <link>https://gabubuavailable.github.io/news/cont/00005.html</link>
    <guid>0000000005</guid>
    <pubDate>2022-07-07</pubDate>
    <description>
      <p>Welcome! Today we're gonna talk about 2 "newses"?</p>
      <p>I'll explain very short this time. If you want to read the full news, here's the link: "https://gabubuavailable.github.io/news/cont/00005.html"</p>
      <p>So, the good news is about the NUS and the Wii Shop Channel. The server is back and now you can use the WSC like it was after clossing it lmao.</p>
      <p>The bad news is about a Discord bot. Or most likely an app which you can authorize with your Discord account. That app adding you to a Discord server with the owner telling you that "There is no escape :skull:".</p>
    </description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Time to move from bloated softwares to less-bloated softwares</title>
    <link>https://gabubuavailable.github.io/news/cont/00004.html</link>
    <guid>0000000004</guid>
    <pubDate>2022-03-28</pubDate>
    <description>
      <p>Welcome! Today we're gonna talk about bloated softwares and why you should move to less-bloated softwares. Are you ready? I think so. ;)</p>
      <p>+ What "bloated" means?</p>
      <p>"Bloated" means overlarge and excessively fat. Something that's way bigger than the original product. Bloated softwares meaning the same thing, a simple software full of random spywares, shits and so on.</p>
      <p>+ Why should we move to less-bloated?</p>
      <p>Using a bloated softwares would "eat" all your resources. A very good example is Google Chrome and Chromium based browsers. If you 2 tabs openned, it would fill your RAM memory and then starting lagging. Another example is the Microsoft UWP apps. I mean seriously, exists .exe files and they are less-bloated than the UWP shits. And now let's talk about the less-bloated alternatives (some of them of course).</p>
      <p>+ Less-bloated alternatives</p>
      <p>Okay so you learned something today but the question is "Yeah but... uhm... what softwares should I use then?". Lemme make a list for you.</p>
      <p>For Google Chrome and Chromium based browsers: LibreWolf, Firefox and Surf</p>
      <p>For VLC and Windows Media Player: mpv and ncmpcpp+mpc+mpd+dmpc</p>
      <p>For GNOME (not a software but still bloated): XFCE and LXQt</p>
      <p>For Google (again, not a software but full of trackers): searx</p>
      <p>And so on... You can find more on the internet.</p>
      <p>I hope you understood why you should move to less-bloated softwares. And I hope you enjoyed while reading this news. Have a great day o/</p>
    </description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Wii Shop and DSi Shop are offline and nobody knows why</title>
    <link>https://gabubuavailable.github.io/news/cont/00003.html</link>
    <guid>0000000003</guid>
    <pubDate>2022-03-26</pubDate>
    <description>
        <p>The Wii Shop and DSi Shop channels have been down for days, prompting speculation that Nintendo may have pulled the plug on both storefronts without warning. </p>
        <p>It has been impossible to buy new content on either store for a while now, but the fact that console owners are unable to retrieve products they've already purchased is far from ideal. Anybody attempting to access either storefront will be met with an error code, although there is speculation that Nintendo's main server remains online due to the fact third-party tools like NUSDownloader can reportedly still be used to download titles.</p>
        <h2>!!!UPDATE!!!</h2>
        <p>Nintendo sent a statement about that problem. They say that Wii Shop Channel and Nintendo DSi Shop are currectly undergoing maintenance and they would provide an update at a later day.</p>
        <p>I hope they would fix that and Open Shop Channel replacement would be done. We wouldn't know when they will finally close these shops</p>
        <h3>Credit: <a href="https://gamedeveloper.com">gameveloper.com</a></h3>
    </description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Former TikTok moderators sue over emotional toll of "extremely disturbing" videos</title>
    <link>https://gabubuavailable.github.io/news/cont/00002.html</link>
    <guid>0000000002</guid>
    <pubDate>2022-03-26</pubDate>
    <description>
        <p>Finally, after so much years of cringe, crime, drama, fights, swearing and many shits on tiktok, former TikTok moderators sue over emotional toll of these kind of videos.</p>
        <p>I'm gonna explain why TikTok is the worst place and why we need to move from it or just uninstall the app.</p>
        <h2>+ The kids</h2>
        <p>I don't have problems with kids but they stay on TikTok even they are 5 years old. TikTok minimum age is 13 on almost every country but sadly the kids doesn't respect that rule. Making a false claim your account would be banned permanently. So kids, if you read this, you better wait until you'll get 13 instead of being cringe on TikTok. Thank you.</p>
        <h2>+ Cringe, crime, drama, nudity and pornographic gestures</h2>
        <p>Yeah... maybe you realized when you readed the subtitle. On TikTok you can see livestream with girls acting like a pornigraphic star or videos with boys or girls almost naked or even fully naked. And remember that this app is 13+, not 18+ app. So please move to PornHub instead... Seriously... You're gonna brainwash kid heads and I think you don't need that...</p>
        <h2>+ Moderators</h2>
        <p>Speaking of moderating and disturbing videos, who moderate that community? Why there are so many cringe and disturbing videos? Oh wait... Lemme tell you. Nobody moderates the community... That's just a stupid bot that makes everything. From checking the videos until reporting to the user. I tried this experiment and it was awful. I started to post normal contents on TikTok (REMEMBER: NORMAL CONTENTS. NO PORNOGRAPHY, NO CRINGE, NO DISTURBING VIDEOS). Guess what? After a few days I've got banned for literally nothing... And these TikTokers with pornographic gestures with their big *ss and b**bs and they don't get banned... Like wtf. You TikTok gonna hire moderators for checking the videos, not using a shit retarded bot that bannes every normal user.</p>
        <h2>+ In conclusinon...</h2>
        <p>Don't use TikTok. Or if you never used don't install it... That's a shit community with all retarded cringe kids and girls with idk poses and almost naked... That was my opinion about TikTok. If you want, you can take this post as a refference. I was Gabubu and I hope you liked it. Cya o/</p>
    </description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>GNOME 42 is here!</title>
    <link>https://gabubuavailable.github.io/news/cont/00001.html</link>
    <guid>0000000001</guid>
    <pubDate>2022-03-25</pubDate>
    <description>
        <p>The new version of GNOME called GNOME 42 is finally here with the greatest updates.</p>
        <p>The new GNOME 42 comes with new features (excludind that big window buttons and the same dock and topbar)</p>
        <p>Now it comes with System Wide Dark Mode which is a great feature for who really wants dark mode on every GUI softwares. They improved the Screen Capture and Recording. Streamline Interface (which almost all DE and WM have that since long time ago), Better and powerful text editor and file explorer (still awful in my opinion) and is way faster (idk).</p>
        <p>These informations are provided by their YouTube channel</p>
        <p>Source: https://youtu.be/du-2QpWbiLU</p>
    </description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>First post</title>
    <link>https://gabubuavailable.github.io/news/cont/00000.html</link>
    <guid>0000000000</guid>
    <pubDate>2022-03-23</pubDate>
    <description>
        <p>Welcome to gabubu news! Here I'll try to do my best and post Wii and tech related news. :D</p>
        <p>It might be hard but I'll try lol. Enjoy and enable notifications for upcomming news ;)</p>
   </description>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>
